[{"answer": "Well, I think what happened in Sandy Hook was really a turning point.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "What to you resonates?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I think -- I think there should be mental health for people who have mental health problems.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What do -- what do you think we can sensibly do?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Better treatment.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Better treatment, better funding?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, I think as a mother of four, sending my kids out to school every day, I think that's why this tragedy affected so many people and hit home with so many people, is that we all go to our homes and send our kids off to school, and every day we assume that they're safe, and we have faith in the teachers and the school that everything is OK.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "I mean, we just need better enforcement of the laws that -- first of foremost better are already put in place.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Our country is founded in such a different way that, you know, so much -- with the Second Amendment even being part of the Constitution, it's so much about protecting liberties because of how we established ourselves as a country.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "And how do we get through that, do you think?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "You know, time, I think, creates this stark realization of what's missing in your life.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "How are they doing, the parents and her little sisters?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I don't think you're quite accurately stating what I -- my job is.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Why is that the solution?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, guns are prohibited in the airplane.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What is your answer for that?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, certainly, you need to look beyond simply a trained, armed presence.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "How do you kind of regulate that?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "We'll give them what they need to get to do the job to protect the children.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "What weapon will you give your trained security people?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "This is not -- this is the -- the experts, the school safety experts, the national law enforcement people, they will recommend what is the best way to protect the children in this environment.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "So just to -- just to clarify, would you give them AR- 15s?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I would give them a weapon so they could take the shooter out.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "What would you do?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I disagree with your point.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "So I'm asking you again, just to clarify, would you give these trained people you're going to train up AR-15 assault rifles?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I think that Congress could pass a half a dozen laws just like they did with the ban on Columbine, and yet the tragedy occurred.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "But just very quickly, you don't think removing AR-15s would help safety?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, first, I have to say I'm thankful that you keep this dialogue going.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What do you think of it?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I thought the president had it absolutely right today.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Is that the way you're going to make a Sandy Hook stop and just say, we'll just sell, what, hundreds of thousands of more guns and put armed guards in every school in America?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "I'm a gun owner.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "When people say to you, John, as they say to me, you're anti-the Constitution, you're anti-the Second Amendment, I'm entitled to all these assault weapons, what do you say?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "They need to personally come to my house, Piers.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What are you looking for?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "OWE: It was sad.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Nobody called, nobody rang?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I was -- I was really surprised that it wasn't closer.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "What did you make of the race, in the end?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I can't believe that President Obama turned out bigger numbers than he thought -- than a lot of people thought he would.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Yeah?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I thought of you, funny enough, because I was watching -- rewatching, for the third time, the entire \"West Wing\" phenomenon, all seven seasons.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "It's a part, I think, of how our country was formed.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Why is it so political in America?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "OWE: I have three.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "How many do you have?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I don't have an assault weapon.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "What types?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "You have handguns?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Look, I wouldn't because -- look, I like guns, and I don't own an assault rifle.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "As a gun owner, you would have no problem if President Obama said, I really want to push for these assault rifles, in particular, to be taken out of circulation?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "But if they don't do that, as you point out, it's not really a ban, is it?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "First of all, I probably watch more cable news than any human should be.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Were you as enthralled as everybody else?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "He actually came to visit the day I did the closing argument.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Did you get to meet Jeff Ashton?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Which was --", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I almost didn't want to go back and see him for fear he would give me the \"oh, boy\" face.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What did he say to you?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I'm there, my friend.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "I want you for my Lifetime movie?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "George Anthony.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Like whom?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "It's my personal opinion that she absolutely had something to do with her daughter's death.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Would you have personally convicted Casey Anthony, the more you now know about the case?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "This one would be a tough one, Piers.", "docId": "130114pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Do you have any sympathy for the people that get caught up in these things?", "qSentId": 624}]